<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<ModMetaData>
	<name>Diamond Industry Harmacy</name>
	<author>Mario55770</author>
	<packageId>Mario.DIH</packageId>
	<supportedVersions>
		<li>1.3</li>
	</supportedVersions>
	<description>
		Brought to you by the exclusive Diamond Industries, the harmacy. Featuring better drug production, poisons, medicines, and more, including antidotes.
		For legal reasons, Diamond Industry executives require warnings informing users to not load poisons into the slot labeled poison, as that would create a chemical weapon.
		Welcome to the Diamond Industry Harmacy Beta Release
		Current features
		Poison melee and ranged weapons. Poison consumed only on a hit. Automatically configured to use all weapons that are implemented correctly(in other words, should be cross mod compatible unless they did something weird)
		New gui widget, under the assign tab, pick what poison a pawn should use, and they'll automatically apply it.
		Poison is consumed on a hit, make sure to keep stocked up.
		Bulk Drug Lab. Automatically gets recipes and makes a bulk version, even if from other mods. Less work, and faster speeds, so your yayo and poison piles grow.
		Milk snakes.
		Cobras and toxic spikes and fangs have been swapped to use cobra venom and midnight murder respectively.
		Three new poisons, Cobra Venom, Brick Knockout, and Midnight Murder.
		Cobra Venom is a potent poison which specializes in making everything worse. Causing necrosis in most open wounds, increasing the victims bleed rate, weakening most stats slightly, and rarely causing heart attacks.
		Brick Knockout is an anesthetic, which confers primarly pain tolerance and a loss of consciousness. For those well versed in Rimworld...this might be sounding a bit familiar. This assists in capturing pawns.
		Midnight Murder is a combat poison through and through. It excels in downing pawns, painfully and dangerously.
		Bug reports require a hugslib at minimum, as well as a description of the problem.
		Suggestions for other mods for me to add compatiblity with are welcome.
		Pending features, toggle between a hit using poison or not.
		Poison raiders.
		Antivenoms, and possible rework of how the hediff applies. (Give it its own system, comparable to a hybrid of toxic buildup, and diseases)
		Minor visual fixes(Incorrect capatalization, cosmetic bugs like that)
		Otimization and balance.

		Credit to Djeeshka for the harmroot plant's texture.
		Discord  https://discord.gg/FqVaCUdPeK

		Github https://github.com/Mario55770/DShield-Trap-Framework
	</description>
</ModMetaData>